Even a living Buddha
wouldn't tutor me for no reason.
Sigh.
Could he have found out?
Why does he look a bit familiar?
Our key project is set up in Xihai City this time
because the supporting facilities here are complete.
Did you notice?
The head of this group is so young.
He's probably the son of a top executive.
Do you like him?
No.
People like that aren't in the same world as us.
With a large group like this taking the lead,
I guess there will be an investment boom in Xihai.
Why is he studying here too?
Were you staring at me in the hallway just now?
Me?
No, I wasn't.
The plants.
I wanted to see if the plants had been watered.
I'll go take a look.
I thought you needed me for something.
I do have something to ask of you, Senior.
Could you help tutor me?
Tutor you?
Yeah.
Please, Senior.
Oh, I see.
So how much are you going to pay for the tutoring?
Can we exchange it for something else, Senior?
Your Ans Group is so rich.
How could I afford it?
Wait a minute.
What did you just say?
Can I exchange it for something else?
No.
Your Ans Group is so rich.
Where did you hear that from?
Ans Group.
Is that a secret?
Yin Zixi,
take your materials
and find me in the broadcasting room later.
How does he know my name?
Are you sure you're not returning to the Student Council?
If I could,
I wouldn't even return to school.
Ugh.
This corporate debt
is an adult's matter.
Your father had you come back to school
for a good reason, of course.
Sir.
If your family were about to go bankrupt,
would you still be in the mood to study?
I wouldn't say that.
The more of a crisis he's in,
the less he wants his family to be affected.
If you truly care for your father,
I think the first thing you should consider is
how to successfully finish your college degree.
Right.
Yin Zixi.
Remember,
never reveal your identity at school.
During this sensitive debt period,
the school will also keep your secret.
Why can't I find it anywhere?
Is it really such a wealthy group?
Yeah.
With just one project,
they can shake all the media in Xihai City.
If it's such a wealthy group,
it's possible that you can't find them.
Huh?
Like the Rothschild family in America,
they've been behind the scenes,
controlling the world economy for over 200 years.
Never heard of them.
Of course.
The richer they are, the more mysterious they get.
Why?
Because everyone who had contact with them vanished,
so outsiders wouldn't know of their existence.
Just kidding.
Oh.
A group that can shock Xihai City
shouldn't be impossible to find online.
Did you remember the name wrong?
No.
I didn't get it wrong.
Dear Mr. An,
Sorry to keep you waiting.
This is your student ID, right?
How did he get it?
This is terrible.
So Mr. An has it.
No wonder.
How do you know about me and An'ers Group?
What's so strange about that?
The Yin family is also a noble family.
We know a bit more than ordinary people.
That's normal.
Never heard of it.
Then let me tell you.
Our Yin family
is closely related to the Rothschild family in the US.
This secret,
is now only known to you.
Oh.
Since we've both put our cards on the table,
if there's nothing else,
I'll be leaving.
Since you are already here, Miss Yin,
leaving without making a deal...
Are you feeling guilty?
Of course not.
It's just...
I don't have a say in my family's affairs,
so I probably can't make any deals.
Take a look first.
As long as I don't tell anyone?
It's that simple?
I can tutor you in another subject.
The penalty for breach of contract is only 50,000.
I can add two more zeros.
Fifty thousand it is.
Our big family doesn't sweat the small stuff.
Did you find it?
But the other party needs
this amount.
Five thousand.
Money is not a problem.
As long as it's guaranteed.
I handle things.
You can rest assured.
Someone has already come to buy the answers.
Someone is interfering this time.
There aren't many people taking the makeup exam.
Who is so bold?
It doesn't matter.
This kind of small money
won't affect anything.
Here, look at this.
Teacher!
The classmates are fighting!
Quick, come with me to take a look.
Why are they fighting again?
Didn't they just fight a couple of days ago?
Let's go take a look first.
Oh, let's go.
Mass Communication Theory,
Introduction to Journalistic Psychology,
Explanation of Past Papers,
Notes.
Looks like your disguise went smoothly.
Sigh.
The other party saw through it a long time ago.
Really?
Yeah.
The agreement only says fifty thousand.
Isn't it because he saw
that I'm an ordinary student who can't afford it?
This is trouble.
What's wrong?
Tell me,
why would he tutor you
for no reason?
He wants me to keep his secret.
No.
Only dead people can keep secrets.
Have you finished reading your novel?
I'm serious.
Let me tell you,
even the richest families
always hire a lot of servants, right?
How could they hide it completely?
This tutoring is him screening you,
testing whether you can keep a secret.
Maybe
he is somewhere right now
monitoring us.
Ah.
These are the test answers.
No.
This is a trial given to you by the Rothschild family.
Ha.
Casting Director Xi Chongjing,
Props Assistant Li Kunxiao,
Grip Truck Yi Mingle,
Yi Tong.